This is a long story. You won't be disappointed so in me Amp my boy Joey, I was he was,
took a month road trip across America. Months in we went to Austin, Texas.
Got into to town at about PM and went to the first bar we could find.
We met two ladies, both late s early s cougars. We danced n drank a lot with them.
About min before closing time a married couple comes amp joins our table.
Seemed nice, the cougars knew the couple. We stay until the bar closes.
One of the cougars invited me Amp Joey to her house for a nightcap wthe other cougar joining as well.
Obviously we went, with me driving following her brand new red BMW convertible, we pull into this
ungodly beautiful gated neighborhood w mansions galore. We get to homeowner cougars house and
it's crazy nice. So the of us are out on her back patio drinking wine. Min after getting there,
the married couple that joined us at the bar walks over, they were apparently the next door
neighbors. Married couple tells Joey Amp why they own a bunch of tanning salons throughout
Austin Amp ask if either of us would like a spray tan since they have the equipment next
door in the basement of their multi million dollar home. I am not keen on tanning spray tanning but
Joey was all about it so he goes with the couple, leaving me w both cougars. The of us are on the
patio for about min when we hear glass shatter, not like dropping a coffee mug, LOT of glass
shattering, come from inside homeowner cougars house. In my inebriated state and with complete
yak of regard for what could have caused said shattering I jump up and walk into the house.
The tanning salon husband, who was about, stout amp in shape im, pound soaking wet,
is in the living room with a pickaxe, about featuring long wooden handle, with a T on the end.
Metal ball on one side of the T, and a super sharp point on other. He had shattered his
neighbors very large glass coffee table. He sees me and starts at me w pickaxe cocked back it was
a baseball bat as he is walking towards me he is screaming h is going to kill me amp my buddy.
He swings the pickaxe at my head and it was the sharp end, luckily I stepped back and it went
out inches in front of my forehead. Would have killed me had I not stepped back and let it
strike my temple. He then pulls it back over his head as if he is going to hammer me straight down
on the top of my head. I quickly bare hugged him, allowing me to hold the axe along with him,
but the head of the axe, and my grip on it, is down by his butt amp his arms were over his head
so I luckily had all the leverage as he was much stronger than me. I walk him out into the front
yard in the position, trying to calm him down amp find out wtf happened. As we get to the front yard
grass I see Joey, stark ass naked, running down the street carrying his jeans. I end up getting
the axe and the crazy neighbor man runs into the woods across the street. It was at this point I
look at my car, our only means of transportation on our month road trip. My dr ford taurus has all
windows shattered out, the windshield is spider webbed in different places, back windshield has
spider web. I start thinking about chasing the guy down as I have his axe now. But as that thought
was just developing, a police officer pulls up with lights on. I guess this a good time to tell
you what I learned hours later from Joey, the story of the spray tan. So the wife was giving
said spray tan, husband was watching. She told Joey to take his boxes off, Joey obviously looked
at the husband sideways like dude your wife wants me naked and husband said oh go ahead it's fine.
So he got naked. As soon as he did the wife starts to perform oral sex on him amp the husband said
it's fine Joey, enjoy and he left him alone. Joey apparently thought it was an open invite to
proceed to having sex with her bc that's what he did. She was apparently a loud lover, bc the
husband came back in to see Joey having sex w his wife. He was apparently the yay my wife can give
you oral but don't have sex with her type of guy bc he freaked out. Joey ran and husband began
rampage w pick axe her back to front yard. The cougars had apparently called and explained the
situation, bc the cop immediately asked where the neighbor was. I was livid about my car, the cop
wouldn't let me walk to the driveway from the porch to go look at my car and I ended up in
handcuffs sitting indian style on the patio. More cops show up, they end up finding psycho neighbor
and I.